http://www.ifae.es/eng/legalwarning-english.html

LegalWarning English
eng
cast
cat
About IfaeHomeWelcomeIFAE StructureIFAE FundingIFAE RepositoryIFAE OrganizationPeopleReaching usSpin-offUseful LinksContractor profileSevero Ochoa ProgramThe Barcelona Institute of Science and TechnologyTransparency & AccountabilityExperimentsATLASNeutrinosMAGICCTADESPAUEuclidMedical ImagingVirgoQuantum Computing TechnologiesTheoryStandard ModelBeyond the Standard ModelAstroparticles and CosmologyEngineeringMicroelectronic Services for IndustryIFAE's technology offeringEducationMaster ProgramPhD ProgramSummer fellowships for UndergraduatesBojos per la FísicaLa cara fosca de l’UniversInternational Day of Women & Girls in ScienceCazadores de Rayos GammaOutreach mailing listPhysics Masterclasses at IFAEBIYSCHuman ResourcesHR StrategyWorking at IFAEOpen PositionsScholarshipsHR proceduresNews & EventsNewsEventsPressReportsInternal Newsletters
DATA PRIVACY POLICY
Company name: INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE)
Registered Office: EDIFICI CN CAMPUS UNIVERSITAT AUTÒNOMA DE BARCELONA - 08193 BELLATERRA CERDANYOLA DEL VALLÉS (BARCELONA)
Tax Identification Code: Q-5856257-J
E-mail:
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Website: www.ifae.es
According to the established in the Organic Law 15/1999, of Personal Data Protection (LOPD for its Spanish acronym), its development regulation, and the LSSICE 34/2002, of 11th july, on the Society of Information and Electronic Commerce, INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE)  in obedience to what the LOPD articles 5 and 6 dispose, informs all users which may provide their personal data, that they will be added to an automatic file which is found duly registered at the Data Protection Spanish Agency.
The users expressly accept, willingly and unequivocal, that their personal data will be treated by INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) to perform the next purposes:
Delivery of advertising commercial communications via e-mail, fax, SMS, MMS, social communities or any other electronic or physical means, present or future, which make possible the commercial communications. Said commercial communications will be about products or services offered by INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) , as well as by the collaborators or partners with whom a commercial promotion agreement for their clients has been established. In this case, the third parties will never have access to the personal data. In any case, the commercial communications will be made by INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) and will be about its products and services, related to INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) ’s business sector.
Make statistical studies.
Process orders, requests or any other kind of petitions, which may be made by the user via any contact form put at the user’s disposition by INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) .
INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE)  informs and expressly guarantees the users that their personal data will not be transferred in any case to third companies, and that in case a data transfer were to be made, the express, informed and unequivocal consent from the title holders would be previously requested.
Through the fulfilling and sending of the pertinent forms in this website, the User accepts and authorizes their personal data to be object of automatic treatment by INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE). In case you add third people’s personal data to the website forms, you must obtain, previous to adding them, their consent and inform them of the points contained in the previous paragraphs. Also, in the event that there is an international transfer of data, the user accepting this Privacy Policy consents because it can be made.
All the requested data through INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) are mandatory, since they are necessary for the optimal services provided to the user. In case not all data is to be obtained, INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) does not guarantee that the provided information and services will be completely adjusted to your needs.
To enjoy the intranet the customer will receive in his/her e-mail a username and a password to be entered in the professional area.
INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) guarantees the user the exercise of their rights of access, rectification, cancellation, information and opposition, in the disposed terms of the current legislation. Therefore, and according to the established in the Organic Law 15/1999, of Personal Data Protection (LOPD), you can exercise your rights addressing an express request, attached to a copy of your ID card via the next means:
E-Mail:
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Post Mail: EDIFICI CN CAMPUS UNIVERSITAT AUTÒNOMA DE BARCELONA - 08193 BELLATERRA CERDANYOLA DEL VALLÉS (BARCELONA)
Likewise, the user can unsubscribe from any of the given subscription services sending an e-mail to:
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
In the same way, INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) has adopted all the technical and organization measures needed to guarantee the security and integrity of the personal data that are treated, as well as to avoid loss, alteration and/or access from non-authorized third parties to them.
CURRICULUMS
For the purposes of the provisions of the current legislation on data protection, data providing us your resume are required for the processing of the application and its owners consent to their personal data and CV, including email , available join the file which is responsible INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) , in order to study and / or implementation of this application and for the study and analysis or custom segmented it.
The data are given curriculum that will be kept for a period of one year, after which proceed INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) total destruction.
INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) ensures that all personal data will be used for the purpose, in the manner and with the limitations and rights granted by the Organic Law 15/1999, of Protection of Personal Data. The holder may exercise the rights of opposition, access and information, rectification, deletion of data and revocation of their authorization without retroactive effect, by written communication to INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE), EDIFICI CN CAMPUS UNIVERSITAT AUTÒNOMA DE BARCELONA - 08193 BELLATERRA CERDANYOLA DEL VALLÉS (BARCELONA)
SECURITY
INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) uses information security techniques, generally accepted in the business, such as firewalls, access control procedures and cryptographic mechanisms, all that with the purpose of avoiding the non-authorized data access. To accomplish these purposes, the user/client accepts that the providing party obtains data for the corresponding acknowledgment of the access controls.
INDUSTRIAL AND INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY
This web is owned by INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) The intellectual property rights and the rights of exploitation and reproduction of this web, of its pages, screens, the Information they contain, their appearance and design, and the hyperlinks established from it to other web pages of any subsidiary and/or company dominated by INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE), are of the exclusive property of the same, unless other thing is expressly specified. Any denomination, design and/or logotype, and any product or service offered and reflected in this web page, are brands duly registered by INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE), by its subsidiaries and/or dominated companies or by third parties. Any undue use of the same by people other than their legitimate owner and without the express and unequivocal consent by that owner can be denounced and pursued by all the legal means existing in the Spanish and/or European Community legal system.
The intellectual property rights and brands of third parties are conveniently highlighted and must be respected by everyone gaining access to this page; INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) is not liable for the use that the user may carry out to that regard; the user is solely liable.
You can only download the contents, copy or print any page from this web for a personal and private use. It is forbidden to reproduce, transmit, modify or delete the information, content or warnings from this web without the prior written consent of INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE).
The contents provided by INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) are subject to the rights of intellectual and industrial property and are of the exclusive ownership of INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) or the individuals or legal entities we inform about. With the purchase of a product or service, INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) does not grant the purchaser any right of alteration, exploitation, reproduction, distribution or public communication of the same; INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) reserves all these rights. The assignment of the mentioned rights will require the prior written consent by the holder of the same, so that the client may not put those contents at the disposal of third parties.
The intellectual property extends, apart from the content included in INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE), to its graphs, logotypes, designs, images and source codes used for its programming.
INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) has obtained the information and materials included in the web from sources considered as reliable and, although reasonable measures have been adopted to ensure that the contained information is correct, INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) cannot guarantee that in all moments and circumstances that information is exact, complete, updated and, consequently, you cannot trust it as if it were so. INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) expressly declines any liability for mistakes or omissions in the information contained in the pages of this web.
INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) reserves the power to modify, suspend, cancel or restrict the content of the web, the links or the information obtained through it, with no need for a prior warning. It in no case assumes any liability as a consequence of the incorrect use of the web by the user, both of the information and of the services contained in it.
In no case shall INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE)  its branch offices and/or work centres, directors and/or attorneys, employees and, in general, the authorised staff be liable for any type of damage, losses, claims or expenses of any type, if they are the result, directly and indirectly, of both the use and/or diffusion of the web or the information acquired or accessed by or through it, or of its computer viruses, of operation failures or of interruptions in the service or transmission, or of failures in the line when using the web, both by direct connection and by links or other means, constituting for all legal purposes a warning to any user that these possibilities and events can take place.
INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE) is not liable for the webs that are not its own, to which you can access by links, or for any content put at the disposal of third parties. Any use of a link or access to a web that is not its own, will be performed voluntarily and at the exclusive risk of the user. INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE)  does not recommend or guarantee any of the information obtained through a link, and is not liable for any loss, claim or damage arising from the use or bad use of a link, or from the information obtained through it, including other links or webs, for the interruption in the service or the access, or for the attempt to use a link or to use it badly, both when connecting to the web of INSTITUT DE FÍSICA D’ALTES ENERGIES (IFAE)  and when gaining access to the information of other webs from the same.
GOVERNING LAW AND JURISDICTION
The applicable law in case of dispute or conflict of the interpretation of the terms that define this privacy policy, as well as any other question related with the services in this website will be the Spanish Law.
About IfaeHomeWelcomeIFAE StructureIFAE FundingIFAE RepositoryIFAE OrganizationPeopleReaching usSpin-offUseful LinksContractor profileSevero Ochoa ProgramThe Barcelona Institute of Science and TechnologyTransparency & AccountabilityExperimentsATLASNeutrinosMAGICCTADESPAUEuclidMedical ImagingVirgoQuantum Computing TechnologiesTheoryStandard ModelBeyond the Standard ModelAstroparticles and CosmologyEngineeringMicroelectronic Services for IndustryIFAE's technology offeringEducationMaster ProgramPhD ProgramSummer fellowships for UndergraduatesBojos per la FísicaLa cara fosca de l’UniversInternational Day of Women & Girls in ScienceCazadores de Rayos GammaOutreach mailing listPhysics Masterclasses at IFAEBIYSCHuman ResourcesHR StrategyWorking at IFAEOpen PositionsScholarshipsHR proceduresNews & EventsNewsEventsPressReportsInternal Newsletters
Institut de Física d'Altes Energies (IFAE) .Edifici Cn, Universitat Autònoma de Barcelona (UAB), E-08193 Bellaterra (Barcelona), Spain© 2011 IFAE. All rights reserved. See also legal warning, cookies policy and privacy policy in social networks.
We use own and third-party cookies to improve our services by analyzing your browsing habits. If you continue browsing, we will consider that you allow us to use them. You can change the settings or get more information on our "Cookies policy".I accept cookies from this site. Agree
